Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5 1870-2017
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5
- General Telephone & Electronics Corp., Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Speak Up!, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Electronic Components News, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
- General Tire, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Glass Packaging Institute, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Glass Packagers Cite Gains Despite, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    No. 4-80 Sept. 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Paths to Progress: Glass Packaging For People, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Materials Currently Available From The Glass Packaging Institute, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Glass Packaging News, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Glass Packaging Institute, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: News Release, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    June 24. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: News Release, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    June 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: News Release, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    April 30. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: News Release, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    No. 2-81 April 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Foster-Forbes Joins Glass Packaging Institute, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    No.1-81 Feb 11. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Glass Recycling, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: The Earth's Future, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
- B.F. Goodrich Company, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Perspective, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
    June Vol. 10 No. 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Perspective, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
    May Vol. 10 No. 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: BFG Today, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
    May-June Vol. 4 No. 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: BFG Today, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
    March-April Vol. 4 No. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Viewpoint, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: BFG Citizen, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Designing A Decade, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: BFG Citizen, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: BF Goodrich, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Human Resources Careers Information, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: BF Goodrich: A History, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: BF Goodrich Chemical and Aerospace Information, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: BF Goodrich Chemicals and Aerospace Information, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: BF Goodrich Chemicals and Aerospace Information, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: No Blimp. Chemical and Aerospace, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: BF Goodrich Chemicals and Aerospace, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 18: BFG Today, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Vol. 12 No. 7 Aug. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: BFG Today, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Vol. 12 No. 2 Feb. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: BFG Today, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Vol 11 No 1 Jan/Feb. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: BFG Today, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Vol 12 No 6 Jun/July. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Profile, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 23: Matching Gift Program, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Good Year Tire & Rubber Company, Publication (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Pay For Performance Salary Administration Program, Publication (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: History of Goodyear, Publication (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: A History of The Goodyear Tire & Rubber Company 1989-1982, Publication (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: GO: The Goodyear Tire Dealer Magazine, Publication (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Jan-Feb. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: World of Opportunities at Goodyear, Publication (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: R&D World, Publication (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Vol 5 No 1 Jan. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: A History of The Goodyear Tire & Rubber Company 87th Anniversary 1989-1985, Publication (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: World of Opportunities at Goodyear, Publication (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Benefits for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Good Year Tire & Rubber Company, Publication (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: First Class, Publication (Box 15, Folder 7)
    July 31. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Wingfoot Clan Akron Edition, Publication (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Vol 73 Thursday, March 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Triangle, Publication (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Vol. 66 No. 1 Jan. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Messenger, Publication (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Vol. 24 No. 4 Fourth Quarter. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Wingfoot Clan Retiree Roundup, Publication (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: The Wingfoot Clan Retiree Roundup, Publication (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Grand Hotel, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Employment Application Admittance Information, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Grand Hotel Management Services, Inc. Employment Agreement, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Graphic Arts Employers of America (GAE), Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: New Directions in Employee Relations and Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Wages and Compensation for the Printing Industry, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Absence & Lateness, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
    By Louise Pitone. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Who's Leading the Printing Industry?, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Who's Leading the Printing Industry, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Computer Graphic Networks, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: GAE Ready or Not A Retirement Planning Review, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Employee Stock Ownership Plans: An Introduction for the Printing and Graphics Arts Industry, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Hire News, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
    May 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: GAE Negotiation Kit, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: GAE Today, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: Controlling Unemployment Costs, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 13: Basic Economic Data, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: Quality Circles - An Introduction for Management, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 15: Quality Circles - An Introduction for Management, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
- GAE, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Special Study Series, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.81:no.2 (1981:November). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Special Study Series, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Special Study Series, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.83:no.1 (1983:March). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Special Study Series, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Special Study Series, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.83:no.2 (1983:April). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Special Study Series, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Special Study Series, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.83:no.3 (1983:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Special Study Series, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Special Study Series, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.83:no.4 (1983:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Special Study Series, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: Special Study Series, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.83:no.1-a (1983:June 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Special Study Series, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Special Study Series, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.85:no.2 (1985:Aug. 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Special Study Series, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.87:no.1 (1987:Mar. 5). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Special Study Series, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: Special Study Series, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.87:no.1a (1987:Mar. 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Bulletin, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.87:no.1 (1987:May 4). Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Bulletin, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.87:no.2 (1987:May 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Bulletin, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.87:no.3 (1987:May 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Bulletin, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.83:no.17 (1983:Nov. 22). Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Bulletin, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.84:no.5 (1984:July 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Q&A, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.82:no.1 (1982:Mar. 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Q&A, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Item 24: Q&A, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.83:no.1 (1983:June 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Q&A, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Item 26: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.83:no.4 (1983:Jan. 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.83:no.5 (1983:Feb. 14). Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.83:no.6 (1983:Mar. 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.83:no.8 (1983:Apr. 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.83:no.9 (1983:May 4). Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.83:no.10 (1983:June 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.83:no.11 (1983:July 5). Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.83:no.12 (1983:Aug. 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.83:no.13 (1983:Aug. 31). Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.83:no.14 (1983:May 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.83:no.17 (1983:Oct. 11). Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.83:no.18 (1983:June 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.83:no.19 (1983:Nov. 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.83:no.20 (1983:July 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.83:no.22 (1983:July 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.83:no.23 (1983:Aug. 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.83:no.24 (1983:Aug. 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.84:no.1 (1984:Sep. 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.84:no.1 (1984:Sep. 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.84:no.2 (1984:Oct. 5). Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.84:no.3 (1984:Oct. 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.84:no.4 (1984:Oct. 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.84:no.4 (1984:Nov. 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.84:no.5 (1984:Nov. 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 50: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.84:no.6 (1984:Feb. 28). Item is in English.
  - Item 51: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.84:no.7 (1984:Apr. 26). Item is in English.
  - Item 52: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.84:no.8 (1984:May 31). Item is in English.
  - Item 53: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.84:no.9 (1984:June 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 54: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.84:no.9 (1984:July 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 55: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.84:no.10 (1984:July 26). Item is in English.
  - Item 56: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.84:no.13 (1984:Sep. 26). Item is in English.
  - Item 57: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.84:no.14 (1984:Oct. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 58: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.84:no.15 (1984:Nov. 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 59: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.84:no.16 (1984:Nov. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 60: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.84:no.17 (1984:Nov. 27). Item is in English.
  - Item 61: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.84:no.18 (1984:Dec. 27). Item is in English.
  - Item 62: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.84:no.19 (1984:Feb. 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 63: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.84:no.20 (1984:Mar. 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 64: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.84:no.21 (1984:Apr. 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 65: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.84:no.22 (1984:May 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 66: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.84:no.23 (1984:June 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 67: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.85:no.1 (1985:June 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 68: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.85:no.2 (1985:Aug. 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 69: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.85:no.3 (1985:Sep. 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 70: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.85:no.4 (1985:Nov. 14). Item is in English.
  - Item 71: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.85:no.5 (1985:Dec. 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 72: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.85:no.6 (1985:Dec. 31). Item is in English.
  - Item 73: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.85:no.7 (1985:Feb. 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 74: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.85:no.8 (1985:Mar. 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 75: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.85:no.9 (1985:Apr. 7). Item is in English.
  - Item 76: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.85:no.10 (1985:Apr. 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 77: Around the Bargaining Loop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    v.85:no.11 (1985:May 22). Item is in English.
- GAE, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.84:no.2 (1984:Jan. 27). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.84:no.3 (1984:Feb. 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.84:no.4 (1984:Feb. 20). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.84:no.5 (1984:Mar. 20). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.84:no.6 (1984:Mar. 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.84:no.7 (1984:Apr. 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.84:no.8 (1984:Apr. 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.84:no.11 (1984:June 20). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.84:no.12 (1984:June 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.84:no.24 (1985:Dec. 14). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.85:no.1 (1985:Jan. 8). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.85:no.2 (1985:Jan. 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.85:no.3 (1985:Feb. 4). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.85:no.5 (1985:Mar. 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.85:no.6 (1985:Mar. 14). Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.85:no.7 (1985:Apr. 5). Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.85:no.8 (1985:Apr. 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.85:no.9 (1985:May 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.85:no.10 (1985:May 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.85:no.11 (1985:June 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.85:no.12 (1985:June 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.85:no.13 (1985:July 8). Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.85:no.14 (1985:July 17). Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.85:no.15 (1985:July 25). Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.85:no.17 (1985:Aug. 16). Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.85:no.17 (1985:Aug. 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.85:no.18 (1985:Sep. 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.85:no.19 (1985:Sep. 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.85:no.20 (1985:Oct. 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.85:no.21 (1985:Nov. 7). Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.85:no.22 (1985:Nov. 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.85:no.23 (1985:Dec. 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.85:no.24 (1985:Dec. 27). Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.86:no.1 (1986:Jan. 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.86:no.2 (1986:Jan. 22). Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.86:no.3 (1986:Feb. 5). Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.86:no.4 (1986:Feb. 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.86:no.5 (1986:Mar. 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.86:no.6 (1986:Mar. 27). Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.86:no.7 (1986:Apr. 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.86:no.8 (1986:Apr. 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.86:no.9 (1986:May 8). Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.86:no.10 (1986:May 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.86:no.11 (1986:June 4). Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.86:no.12 (1986:June 25). Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.86:no.13 (1986:July 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.86:no.14 (1986:July 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.86:no.15 (1986:July 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.86:no.16 (1986:Aug. 14). Item is in English.
  - Item 50: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.86:no.17 (1986:Sep. 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 51: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.86:no.18 (1986:Sep. 22). Item is in English.
  - Item 52: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.86:no.19 (1986:Oct. 8). Item is in English.
  - Item 53: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.86:no.20 (1986:Oct. 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 54: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.86:no.21 (1986:Nov. 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 55: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.86:no.22 (1986:Nov. 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 56: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.86:no.22 (1986:Nov. 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 57: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.86:no.24 (1986:Dec. 4). Item is in English.
  - Item 58: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.87:no.2 (1987:Feb. 2). Item is in English.
  - Item 59: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.87:no.3 (1987:Feb. 16). Item is in English.
  - Item 60: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.87:no.4 (1987:Mar. 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 61: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.87:no.5 (1987:Mar. 11). Item is in English.
  - Item 62: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.87:no.7 (1987:Apr. 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 63: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.87:no.8 (1987:Apr. 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 64: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.87:no.9 (1987:May 4). Item is in English.
  - Item 65: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.87:no.10 (1987:May 28). Item is in English.
  - Item 66: Industrial Relations Bits & Pieces, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    v.87:no.11 (1987:June 1). Item is in English.